http://www.mayah.com/en/privacy-policy.html

Privacy policy - MAYAH Communications
Skip to main navigation (Press Enter). Skip to main content (Press Enter).
Search ...
Privacy policy
Responsible party pursuant to data protection laws, in particular the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), is
Detlef Wiese, CEO MAYAH Communications GmbH Am Soeldnermoos 17 85399 Hallbergmoos, Germany
Your rights as the data subject
You can exercise the following rights at any time using the contact details of our data protection officer:
Information on your data stored by us and the processing thereof (Art. 15 GDPR),
Rectification of inaccurate personal data (Art. 16 GDPR),
Deletion of your data stored by us (Art. 17 GDPR),
Restriction of the data processing, provided that we may not delete your data due to legal obligations (Art. 18 GDPR),
Objection to the processing of your data with us (Art. 21 GDPR), and
Data portability, provide that you have consented to the data processing or have entered into a contract with us (Art. 20 GDPR).
If you have given us consent, you may withdraw it at any time, which will remain in effect in the future.
You can contact a supervisory authority with a complaint at any time, e.g. the supervisory authority of the state of your residence or the authority that oversees us as the responsible party.
You’ll find a list of supervisory authorities (for the non-public area) with their respective addresses at: https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Infothek/Anschriften_Links/anschriften_links-node.html.
Collecting general information during a visit to our website
Type and purpose of the processing
When you access our website – i.e. if you do not register or submit information – information of a general nature will be collected automatically. This information (server log files) contains the type of web browser, the operating system used, the domain name of your Internet service provider, your IP address and the like.
It is processed in particular for the following purposes:
Ensuring an unproblematic website connection,
Ensuring seamless use of our website,
Analysis of system security and stability, as well as
For additional administrative purposes.
We will not use your data to draw conclusions about your person. This type of information will be statistically analysed by us if necessary to optimise our website and its underlying technology.
Legal basis
The processing occurs according to Art. 6 Para. 1 (f) GDPR, based on our legitimate interest in improving the stability and functionality of our website.
Recipients
Recipients of the data may be technical service providers, who work on the operation and maintenance of our website as the processor.
Retention period
The data will be deleted as soon as they are no longer required for the reason they were collected. This is generally the case, after the respective session has ended, for data that are used to make the website available.
Mandatory or required provision
The provision of the aforementioned personal data is neither legally nor contractually mandatory. Without the IP address however, the service and functionality of our website are not guaranteed. Furthermore, individual services can be unavailable or limited. For this reason, an objection is excluded.
Cookies
Type and purpose of the processing
Like many other websites, we use so-called ‘cookies’. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your device (laptop, tablet, smartphone, etc.) when you visit our website.
With cookies, we receive certain information such as IP address, type of browser and operating system used.
Cookies cannot be used to start programs or to transmit viruses to a computer. Based on the information contained in cookies, we can facilitate your navigation of our site and properly display our webpages for you.
The data collected by us will not be shared with third parties under any circumstances nor will a link to personal data be created without your consent.
Of course, you can view our website without cookies. Internet browser are regularly configured to accept cookies. In general, you can disable the use of cookies via your browser settings at any time. Please use your Internet browser’s help function to learn how to change these settings, and keep in mind that individual features of our website may not work if you have disabled the use of cookies.
Retention period and cookies used
If you allow us to use cookies, via your browser settings or consent, the following cookies may be utilised on our web pages:
debug by mayah.com, persistent
In the following sections, we provide you with information concerning how these cookies can (also) pertain to personal data.
In your browser settings, you can delete individual cookies or the entire set of cookies. You will also find information and instructions on how to delete these cookies or prevent them from being saved in advance. The following links provide the information you’ll need for the respective browser providers:
Mozilla Firefox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored
Internet Explorer: https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies
Google Chrome: https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?hl=en
Opera: https://www.opera.com/o/ie-simple
Safari: https://support.apple.com/kb/PH17191?locale=de_DE&viewlocale=en_US
Newsletter
Type and purpose of the processing
Your data will be used exclusively to send you the newsletter you subscribed for via e-mail. We request your name so that we can address you personally in the newsletter and identify you as needed should you want to exercise your rights as a data subject.
To receive the newsletter, providing your e-mail address is sufficient. When you subscribe to our newsletter, the data you provide will be used exclusively for this purpose. Subscribers can also be notified by e-mail about circumstances that are relevant to the service or registration (such as changes to the newsletter offer or technical matters).
We need a valid e-mail address to complete your registration. In order to verify that a registration is actually made by the owner of an e-mail address, we utilise the ‘double opt-in’ procedure. To this end, we log the newsletter subscription request, when a confirmation e-mail is sent and the receipt of the requested reply. Additional data is not collected. The data will be used exclusively for sending the newsletter and will not be shared with third parties.
Legal basis
Based on your express consent (Article 6 (1) a DSGVO), we will send you our newsletter on a regular basis or comparable information via e-mail to your specified e-mail address.
The consent to save and use your personal data for the newsletter may be withdrawn at any time and remain in effect in the future. Every newsletter contains a corresponding link, and you can also unsubscribe on this website at any time or inform us of your cancellation via the contact option indicated at the end of this privacy policy.
Recipients
Recipients of the data may be the processors.
Retention period
Data are only processed in this context provided that the corresponding consent has been given. The data will be deleted thereafter.
Mandatory or required provision
The provision of your personal data is voluntary, based solely on your consent. Unfortunately, we cannot send you our newsletter without your consent.
Contact form
Type and purpose of the processing
The data you enter are used for individual communication with you. A valid e-mail address and your name are required for this communication, which serves to organize your inquiry and the respective subsequent reply. Providing additional information is optional.
Legal basis
The processing of the data entered in the contact form occurs on the basis of a legitimate interest (Art. 6 Para. 1 (f) GDPR).
By providing the contact form, our aim is to facilitate an uncomplicated means for you to contact us. The information you enter will be used to process the inquiry and saved for possible follow-up questions.
If you contact us to request an offer, the processing of the information provided in the contact form will occur in order to implement pre-contractual measures (Art. 6 Para. 1 (b) GDPR).
Recipients
Recipients of the data may be the processors.
Retention period
The data will be deleted no later than 6 months after processing the inquiry.
Provided that we enter into a contract together, we will use the statutory retention periods in the German Commercial Code (Handelsgesetzbuch) and delete your data according to the respective stipulated deadlines.
Mandatory or required provision
The provision of your personal data is voluntary. However, we can only process your inquiry if you provide us with your name, e-mail address and the reason for your inquiry.
Using Google Analytics
Type and purpose of the processing
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service of Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA (hereinafter: ‘Google’). Google Analytics uses so-called ‘cookies’, i.e. text files that are stored on your computer and allow an analysis of your use of the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is typically transmitted to a Google server in the U.S. and stored there. However, due to the activation of IP anonymisation on these websites, your IP address will be truncated beforehand by Google within the member states of the European Union or in other contracting states of the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be sent to a Google server in the U.S. and truncated there. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, summarise reports on website activities and provide other services related to website and Internet usage to the website operator. The IP address transferred from your browser as part of Google Analytics will not be combined with other data from Google.
The data processing purposes are the website-use analysis and the summary of reports on activities on the website. Based on the use of the website and the Internet, other related services will be provided.
Legal basis
The processing of the data occurs on the basis of the user’s consent (Art. 6 Para. 1 (a) GDPR).
Recipients
The recipient of the data is Google as the processor. For this, we have entered into the corresponding data-processing contract with Google.
Retention period
The deletion of the data occurs as soon as they are no longer necessary for our recording-keeping purposes.
Third country transfers
Google processes your data in the United States of America and is subject to the EU-US Privacy Shield: https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework.
Mandatory or required provision
The provision of your personal data is voluntary, based solely on your consent. If you prevent access, this can lead to functional limitations on the website.
Revocation of consent
You can prevent the storage of cookies by a corresponding setting in your browser software; however, please note that in this case you may not be able to use all the functions of this website in their entirety. Furthermore, you can prevent the collected data generated by the cookie and the data related to your use of the website (including your IP address) being transmitted to Google, as well as the processing of this data by Google, by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available at the following link: browser add-on to deactivate Google Analytics.
In addition, or as an alternative to the browser add-on, you can prevent tracking by Google Analytics on our web pages by clicking this link, which will install an opt-out cookie on your device. This will prevent data collection by Google Analytics for this website and for this browser in the future, as long as the cookie remains installed in your browser.
Profiling:
With the assistance of the tracking tool Google Analytics, the browsing behaviour of the website visitors can be evaluated and their respective interests can be analysed. For this analysis, we create a pseudonymous user profile.
Using Google Maps
Type and purpose of the processing
We use Google Maps on this website. Google Maps is operated by Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (hereinafter ‘Google’). This allows us to show you interactive maps directly on the website, allowing you to conveniently use the map feature.
You’ll find additional information about Google’s data processing on the Google privacy policy page(http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html), where you can also change your personal privacy settings in the data protection center.
Click here (http://www.dataliberation.org/) for detailed instructions on how to manage your own data related to Google products.
Legal basis
Your consent is the legal basis for the integration of Google Maps and the associated data transfer to Google (Art. 6 Para. 1 (a) GDPR).
Recipients
By visiting the website, Google receives information that you have accessed the corresponding subpage of our website. This occurs regardless of whether Google provides a user account that you are logged into or if there is no user account. When you’re logged into Google, your data will be directly assigned to your account.
If you do not want this assignment in your Google profile, you must log out of Google before activating the button. Google stores your data as usage profiles and uses them for advertising, market research and/or tailor-made design of its website. Such an analysis occurs in particular (even for users who are not logged in) to provide needs-based advertising and to inform other users of the social network about your activities on our website. You have the right to object to the formation of these user profiles, but you must submit this objection to Google.
Retention period
We do not collect any personal data via the integration of Google Maps.
Third country transfers
Google processes your data in the United States of America and is subject to the EU-US Privacy Shield https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework.
Revocation of consent
If you do not want Google to collect, process or use information about you via our website, you can disable JavaScript in your browser settings. In this case, you cannot or only partially use our website.
Mandatory or required provision
The provision of your personal data is voluntary, based solely on your consent. If you prevent access, this can lead to functional limitations on the website.
Embedded YouTube videos
Type and purpose of the processing
We embed YouTube videos on several of our websites. The operator of the respective plugins is YouTube, LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA (hereinafter ‘YouTube’). YouTube, LLC is a subsidiary of Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheater Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (hereinafter ‘Google’). When you visit a page with the YouTube plug-in, a connection to YouTube’s servers will be created, which tells YouTube which pages you visit. When you are logged into your YouTube account, YouTube can associate your browsing behaviour with you personally. You can prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account beforehand.
If a YouTube video is started, the provider uses cookies that collect information about user behaviour.
You will find additional information on the purpose and scope of the data collection and its processing by YouTube in the provider’s privacy policy, as well as additional information on your rights and setting options for protecting your privacy (https://policies.google.com/privacy). Google processes your data in the United States of America and is subject to the EU-US Privacy Shield https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework.
Legal basis
Your consent is the legal basis for the integration of YouTube and the associated data transfer to Google (Art. 6 Para. 1 (a GDPR).
Recipients
Visiting YouTube automatically triggers a connection to Google.
Retention period and revocation of consent
Everyone who has disabled the storage of cookies for the Google ad programme will not have to expect any cookies when watching YouTube videos. However, YouTube also stores non-personal usage information in other cookies. If you would like to prevent this, you must block the storage of cookies in the browser.
You’ll find additional information on data protection at ‘YouTube’ in the provider’s privacy policy at: https://policies.google.com/privacy.
Third country transfers
Google processes your data in the United States of America and is subject to the EU-US Privacy Shield https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework.
Mandatory or required provision
The provision of your personal data is voluntary, based solely on your consent. If you prevent access, this can lead to functional limitations on the website.
Revision of our privacy policy
We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy so that it always complies with current legal requirements or to implement changes to our services in the privacy policy, e.g. when introducing new services. Your next visit will be subject to the new privacy policy.
Questions for the data protection officer
If you have any questions pertaining to data protection, please send us an e-mail or contact the person responsible for data protection in our organization
Detlef Wiese, CEO MAYAH Communications GmbH +49 171 8305175 This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Revision of our privacy policy
We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy so that it always complies with current legal requirements or to implement changes to our services in the privacy policy, e.g. when introducing new services. Your next visit will be subject to the new privacy policy.
Questions for the data protection officerIf you have any questions pertaining to data protection, please send us an e-mail or contact the person responsible for data protection in our organization.
The privacy policy was created via the activeMind AG Privacy Policy Generator (Version: 2018-09-24).
Legal Notice | Terms | Sitemap | Newsletter | Contact | Privacy policy
In order to provide you with the best online experience this website uses cookies.
By using our website, you agree to our use of cookies.															Learn more
I agree
© 2020 MAYAH Communications
